wholesaleclothing4u.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Notice : Wholesaleclothing4u.com

WholesaleClothing4U.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. At WholesaleClothing4U.com, we make every effort to protect your online order information by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. SSL encrypts your order information to ensure that it remains private and secure. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting WholesaleClothing4U.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

****What Personal Information About Customers Does WholesaleClothing4U.com Gather?****

WholesaleClothing4U.com does not gather personally identifying information about you, unless you choose to provide such information to us. The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at WholesaleClothing4U fashion store. Here are the types of information we gather.

◆We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.

◆When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

◆We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.

◆Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

****What about Cookies?****

Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

****Does WholesaleClothing4U.com Share the Information It Receives?****

We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and order.

****Which Information Can I Access?****

WholesaleClothing4U.com gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.

****Questions****

Questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact Us" link in the side menu. Or you can email us at: sales@wholesaleclothing4u.com
